VO VAN THUAN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Contact information

- 📛 🛮 Jan 1st, 1999
- Male
- 0385148841
- ✓ votuonganvn@gmail.com
- A Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Skills

Language

English, Vietnamese

Soft Skills

Teamwork, Critical Thinking,...

Office Documents

Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Programming Language

C/C++, Python, Assembly

Software Development Life Cycle

V-model, Agile/Scrum

Task Management Tools

GitLab, SVN Tortoise, Redmine/JIRA, IBM ALM Tool

Automotive

AUTOSAR: MCAL/CDD, ECU SW development

Objective

I would like to get an advance level of Software Engineering Industry through joining the freelance projects around C/C++ programming or the equivalent language.

With two-year experience as an Software Engineer, I am trying my best to gain knowledge and practice the mindset of solving problems - the necessary qualities for a good Software Engineer.

Education

University of Science - Vietnam National University

Aug 2017-2021

Major: Computer and Embedded System

GPA: 8.33/10

Work experiences

Bosch Global Software Technologies

Mar 2022-Present

Engineer

Do tasks around the product under leader's assignment:

- Develop communication (COM) module via CAN network: manage transmission/reception for messages, fault/DTC handling, API provision for other modules,...
- Develop customer diagnostics by tester communication: manage supported services (read/write data, security access, communication control, routine control,...)
- Document maintenance via IBM DOORS.
- SW Design and corresponding testing methods (Dynamic/Static Design Test)
- Test strategy for V-model (Unit Test, Integration Test,...)

Main skills: C, Python for Scripting, CAN protocol, IBM environment,...

FPT Software

Mar 2021-Feb 2022

Embedded Software Engineer

Do tasks around the product under leader's assignment:

- Design I2C module from the requirement step-by-step follow as V-model SDLC.
- SW Code maintenance for Embedded and Script.
- Conduct Unit test, Integration test as the test strategy/specification
- Detect the defect in design (if any) and find solutions around the issues.

Main skill: C, Perl and Python for Scripting, I2C communication protocol, GitLab

Certifications

2021: TOEIC Certificate with score 730

2022: Cambrigde EnglishScore with 463 - equivalent with B2 level